MR SHAHNAWAZ BASHIR

PROFILE

Training to become a Full Stack Web Developer using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Django and other great programming languages.

Qualified Transport Manager for Passenger Transport

Authorised Midas and PATS train the trainer

D1 & D category PSV driver + with driver CPC

Over 12 years transport experience on Passenger transport

CONTACT

PHONE: **07535417889**

EMAIL:

Shanbashir1@hotmail.com

HOBBIES

Transport sector Software developing Football Islam Relaxing

EDUCATION

Queens School, WATFORD 1994 - 2000

GCSE - English, Math, Business, IT, Geography & GNVQ Business

West Herts College

2000 - 2002

A levels - Business & IT and web design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lucketts of Watford – Operational Manager

2008 - 2022

Managing over 500 + vehicles daily from coaches, minibuses, ambulances and taxis. The work consisted of private hire routes, Home to school transport, emergency rail work, ambulances NEPTS etc.

Netcom Distribution Purchasing Manager

2002 - 2008

Purchasing computer software and hardware for resellers and Educational sectors

TRAINING AND ACHEIVEMENTS

Code Institute Full Stack Web Developer

- + HTML
- + CSS
- + Javascript
- + Python

PSV Transport Manager Qualified for Passenger Transport – Since 2015 MIDAS & PATS CTA approved Train the Trainer - Since 2021 PSV Driver with Category D and D1 with current CPC entitlement - Since 2012

Koller Approved Wheelchair restraints Training Partner – Since 2012